Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/calebnyong (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

TypeScript
Advanced HTML
Advanced CSS

Certifications

Responsive Web Design Web Design Software Engineering

Caleb Nyong

Frontend Web Developer || Product Designer (Open for full-time opportunities)

Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

Hello, I'm Caleb Nyong, a Software Engineer specializing in Frontend development, and also serving as an Educator and Content Creator. I have a deep passion for delving into fundamental engineering concepts across the Web, whether it's through attending conferences, listening to podcasts, or devouring online articles.

One important aspect about me is my commitment to the 70/30 rule. I firmly believe in approaching each endeavor with 30% expertise and 70% eagerness to learn and expand my knowledge and skill set.

Experience

alx_africa
Software Engineer Intern
February 2022 - April 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Zuri Team, Inc.
Product Design Intern
February 2022 - March 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Education

alx_africa

Software Engineering · (February 2022 - April 2023)

Federal University of Technology Akure

ALX Academy